in the 3
it’s getting deep
we been going tribal in the deep end
maybe, I'm just sowing what I'm reaping
I've been really feeling like the reaper
Cause I'm playing for my
keeps and then I keep them
Turning on the news, I see the reaper
Laying in the sheets and never sleeping
Lately, we've been fighting in
the deep end Lately, I've been
praying for the third world
But it feel like it not reaching I don't
know what he think he reaching for
I might lift the heater and delete him
Smoking on that shit cause I'm a chief
Smoking on that shit cause I'm a chieftain
All my hitters rolling with the leaf, yeah
How I get so cold, my heart is freezing
I know that you gone but I need
you to myself I know that you hurt
from all the pain that you felt
And when I did you wrong, it
make me wanna smoke that pack
I'ma heal the world and I'ma put
it on my back When I wanna go deep
I just bought a bezel, now they
watching on me I just know my
heart is cold, I blame it on me
Pain in our blood, they
gonna feel it when we bleed
Free Palestine, said from
the river to the sea
I know you heard lately
I’m stuck in the slum
forever leave, the past
right in the deep end
What you say, what you
heard, I cannot speak it
Call it even, don't believe
me, gotta believe it
I just wanna take it to the deep end
Running out of time, no time for beefing
Made it out da mud, I had to leave it
Free all my people in Middle Eastern
We been going tribal in the deep end
Maybe I'm just sowing what I'm reaping
I've been really feeling like the reaper
Cause I'm playing for my
keeps and then I keep them
Deep end, deep end, I'm finna leap in
Deep end, running off a deep end
Goalie but I'm not your keeper
Lately, still it’s getting deeper
Pain in my back, I felt that
shit, straight from the jump
I know you heard lately
I’m stuck in the slums
Forever lift, my people out of deep end
Call it even, don't believe
me, gotta believe it
We been going tribal in the deep end
Maybe I'm just sowing what I'm reaping
I've been really feeling like the reaper
Cause I'm playing for my
keeps and then I keep it
Turning on the news to see the reaper
Laying in the sheets and never sleeping
Lately, we been fighting in the deep end
Lately, I've been praying for the 3